Alumni Association; Records ua801
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administration, 1873-1997; Undated; 1; 5.32 cubic ft.
  - Treasurer's Report, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (1-Administration), Folder 37)
  - Ann G. Begam, Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 January 24 (Box 4 (1-Administration), Folder 38)
  - Lorna W. Reamer, Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 June 05 (Box 4 (1-Administration), Folder 39)
  - Lorna W. Reamer, Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 March 24 (Box 4 (1-Administration), Folder 40)
  - Linda J. Murray, Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 September 12 (Box 4 (1-Administration), Folder 41)
  - Linda J. Murray, Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 December 05 (Box 4 (1-Administration), Folder 42)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1987 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 3)
  - Carol Livingston, Interim Director, Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 March 19 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 4)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 June 03 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 5)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 September 17 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 6)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1988 November 19 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 9)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 March 18 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 10)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 June 02 (Box 5 (1-Administration), Folder 11)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 June 02 (Box 6 (1-Administration), Folder 1)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 September 09 (Box 6 (1-Administration), Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1989 November 18 (Box 6 (1-Administration), Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (1-Administration), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 March 24 (Box 6 (1-Administration), Folder 5)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 June 08 (Box 6 (1-Administration), Folder 6)
  - Leadership Summit, Otesaga hotel, 1990 September 14-1990 September 15 (Box 6 (1-Administration), Folder 7-8)
  - Board Retreat, Otesaga Hotel, 1990 September 14-1990 September 16 (Box 7 (1-Administration), Folder 1)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 November 17 (Box 7 (1-Administration), Folder 2)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1991 November 16 (Box 7 (1-Administration), Folder 3)
  - Carol Livingston, Board of Directors Meeting, 1992 June 12 (Box 8 (1-Administration), Folder 1)
  - FIT, Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 March 22 (Box 8 (1-Administration), Folder 2)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Graduate Council of the New York State College for Teachers Alumni Association, Undated (Box 8 (1-Administration), Folder 3)
- Fund-Raising, 1907-2006; Undated; 2; 3.22 cubic ft.
  Series 2 contains records related to Alumni Association fund-raising activities. Please note that the bulk of the series is from the years 1963-1983 with the further majority of this within the decade of the 1970s.
  The earliest fund-raising records are from the first half of the 20th Century and address student loan funds and the Husted Fellowship. Materials document who is eligible for loans, minutes and activities of the beneficiary aid committee, and contributions to the Husted Fellowship.
  Later records from the 1960s document Project Carillon, the fund-raising effort by the Alumni Association to build the Carillon tower which has become a symbol of the University's Uptown Campus. This includes Project Carillon ledgers, lists of pledges, records, events, and general information. The remainder of the series is from the 1970s and 1980s and is composed of correspondence, attendance sheets, donor lists, and balance sheets relating to the Annual Fund in general and the Phonothon specifically.
  Lists of dues payers and balance sheets relating to income from association dues are scattered throughout, as are estate bequests and matching grants. Bequests include information of solicitation of retired alumni, a letter from an alumna suggesting such an action, and several examples of wills or notices of probates showing the results. The matching grants include pamphlets from both the Alumni Association and participating companies such as General Electric. There are also lists and records of the alumni who qualified and participated in those programs.
  Reports such as “A Study of Attitudes and Funding Potentialities of the State University of New York At Albany" and "Visions of Progress" a report conducted by the Alumni Association in 1976 on its own efforts may also be found in this series.
  - Albert H. Husted Fellowship Fund Treasurer's Book, 1907-1910; 1913; Undated (Oversized 3)
  - McClelland Student Loan Fund, ca. 1917; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 1)
  - Beneficiary Aid Fund, 1922; 1924-1935; 1937-1938; 1940-1960 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 2)
  - Alumni Fund Manual and Guidelines, 1963; 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 3)
  - Project Carillon, 1963-1966 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 4)
  - Project Carillon, ca. 1964-1966 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 5)
  - Project Carillon Ledger Records and Solicitations, ca. 1964-1966 (Oversized 4, Folder 3)
  - Reports for Carillon, Alumni, and Special Letter Fund, 1964-1968 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 6)
  - Project Carillon Ledger, 1965-1967 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 7)
  - Project Carillon Records, 1965-1967; 1969; 1970; 1972-1978; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 8)
  - Project Carillon Pamphlets, 1966 June 18 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 9)
  - Alumni Carillon- Donors, Events, and Description, 1966 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 10)
  - Project Carillon Books, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 11)
  - Project Carillon, 1966; 1969; 1970 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 12)
  - Dues, 1967; 1969; 1970 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 13)
  - Alumni Fund Pamphlets, 1969; 1970 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 14)
  - Alumni Association Fund-Raising Letter, Addresses, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 15)
  - General Fund-Raising, 1970; 1971; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 16)
  - Annual Fund-Budgets, Transactions, and Expenditures, 1970-1971; 1973-1983 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 17)
  - Annual Fund, Members, 1970; 1971; 1975; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 18)
  - Dues, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 19)
  - "A Study of Attitudes and Funding Potentialities of the State University of New York State at Albany"-E. LeeMcLean, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 20)
  - Dues, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 21)
  - Annual Fund, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 22)
  - Annual Fund, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 23)
  - Annual Fund and Phonothon, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 24)
  - Class Fund Financial Procedural Manual, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 25)
  - Fund-Raising, Annual Fund Year 1, Reception, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 26)
  - Leadership and Volunteers, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 27)
  - Annual Fund and Phonothon, 1972-1974; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 28)
  - Annual Fund and Alton Bader: Up for Classes, 1972; 1974 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 29)
  - Dues, 1972; 1974; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 30)
  - Annual Fund and Phonothon, 1973 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 31)
  - Dues, Membership, Assets, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 32)
  - Annual Fund and Class Programs, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 33)
  - Annual Fund and Phonothon, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 34)
  - Annual Fund, Planning, and Reception-with photo, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 35)
  - Mailing, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 36)
  - Annual Fund, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 37)
  - Annual Fund, Regional Programs, and Phonothon, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 38)
  - Phonothon, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 39)
  - Regional Programs and Lists, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 40)
  - Regional Programs, Capital District, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 41)
  - Annual Fund and Special Gifts, 1973-1975; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 42)
  - Class REP Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 43)
  - Dr. Burke, Arvid J.-Gifts, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 44)
  - Phonothon, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 45)
  - Phonothon, 1973-1975; Undated (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 46)
  - Annual Fund, Fund Reports and Special Gifts, 1973-1975; 1977 (Box 1 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 47)
  - Annual Fund, Memos and Funds, 1973-1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 1)
  - Annual Fund-Dues, 1973-1977; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 2)
  - Annual Fund-Vendors, Contractors, 1973; 1976-1977; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 3)
  - Annual Fund-Agendas, 1924 January 24; 1978 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 4)
  - Annual Fund-Planning, 1974 December 15 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 5)
  - Annual Fund-Class Letters, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 6)
  - Annual Fund-Reports, News, and Fund-Raising, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 7)
  - Annual Fund-Correspondence, 1974; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 8)
  - Annual Fund and Private Fund-Raising-Includes Correspondence, 1974-1975; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 9)
  - Phonothon Phone Bills, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 11-12)
  - Annual Fund and Roy McErney, 1974-1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 13)
  - Investment Procedures, 1975 September (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 14)
  - Annual Fund-News and Phonothon, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 15)
  - Phonothon, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 16)
  - Annual Fund-Correspondence, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 17)
  - Annual Fund-Phonothon, Pamphlet, and "New Directions", 1975 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 18)
  - Annual Fund-"New Directions", 1975; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 19)
  - Dues, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 20)
  - Phonothon, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 21)
  - Phonothon Sign up and Progress, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 22)
  - Annual Fund, 1975; 1976 January (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 23)
  - Annual Fund-Publications, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 24)
  - Annual Fund, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 25)
  - Annual Fund-General Electric Matching Gifts, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 26)
  - Dues-Solicitations, 1975-1976; 1978; 1980; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 27)
  - Annual Fund-Private Fund-Raising, 1975-1977 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 28)
  - Phonothon and Annual Fund, 1975-1977; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 29)
  - Alumni Fund-Pamphlets, 1975-1979; 1982; 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 30)
  - Estate Bequests, 1975; 1978 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 31)
  - Annual Fund-"Visions of Progress" Report, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 32)
  - Carillon Club Calendar-Pictures, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 33)
  - Project Carillon, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 34)
  - Annual Fund-Memos and Reports, 1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 35)
  - Annual Fund-Outreach, 1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 36)
  - Dues, 1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 37)
  - Phonothon-Photographs, 1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 38)
  - Annual Fund-Club Gifts, 1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 39)
  - Library Benefits, 1976-1979 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 40)
  - Annual Fund-Proposal, 1977 September 23; 1978 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 41)
  - Alumni Fund and Phonothon, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 42)
  - Annual Fund and Phonothon, 1977; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 1)
  - Annual Fund Letters, 1977; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 2)
  - Annual Fund and Phonothon, 1977-1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 3-4)
  - Dues and Annual Fund, 1977-1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 5)
  - Phonothon Letter Mockups, ca. 1977-1978; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 4)
  - Phonothon, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 6)
  - Report on Visit with Leberman, Robert W., 1978 January 05-1978 January 06 (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 7)
  - Authority for Cash Accounts, 1978 March 11 (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 8)
  - Annual Fund, Corporate Resolution for President Michael A. Lampert, 1978 March (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 9)
  - Annual Fund-Gifts and Pledges, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 10)
  - Annual Fund Mailing Guide, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 11)
  - Annual Fund Programs, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 12)
  - Annual Fund-Information Packet, 1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 13)
  - Annual Fund Letter Mockups, 1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 14)
  - Annual Fund Phonothon, 1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 15)
  - Dues-Mailings, 1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 16)
  - Annual Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 17)
  - Phonothon, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 3 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 18)
  - Annual Fund-Dues, 1978-1980; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 1)
  - Annual Fund, 1978-1980; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 2)
  - Annual Fund-Dues, 1979; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 3)
  - Annual Fund-Expenditures and Reports, 1979; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 4)
  - Annual Fund-Reports, 1979; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 5)
  - Annual Fund-Minutes, 1980 September 05 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 6)
  - Annual Fund-Outreach, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 7)
  - Membership Application, 1980-1981 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 8)
  - Annual Fund-Correspondence, 1980-1981; 1983; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 9)
  - Annual Fund, Category Narratives, 1981 August 24 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 10)
  - Annual Fund-Outreach and Pamphlet, 1982; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 11)
  - Annual Fund Resolution, 1983 May 12 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 12)
  - Darcy Arsenburg, Telethon Photographs, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 13)
  - Outreach and Pamphlet, 1983; 1987 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 14)
  - Annual Fund-Outreach, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 15)
  - Planned Giving, 1984; 1994; Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 16)
  - Annual Fund-Outreach, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 17)
  - Annual Fund-Outreach and Pamphlets, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 18)
  - Membership Campaign, Phone-a-thon Materials, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 19)
  - Annual Fund-Board Institutes Changes in Membership Fees, Undated (Box 4 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 20)
  - Annual Fund-Estimated Expenses, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 1)
  - Annual Fund-Gift Lists, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 2)
  - Annual Fund, Phonothon-Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 3)
  - Annual Fund-Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 4)
  - Annual Fund-Transparency, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 5)
  - McClelland Student Loan Fund, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 6)
  - Offices and Board Members, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 7)
  - Regional Programs: Buffalo, Syracuse, Watertown, Binghamton, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 8)
  - Regional Programs-Lists of Potential Donors, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 9)
  - Regional Programs-Washington D.C., Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 10)
  - Transparencies Used for Fund-Raising, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 5)
  - University Development Program, Undated (Box 5 (2-Fund-Raising), Folder 11)
- Subject Files, 1851-2005; Undated; 3; 10.21 cubic ft.
  This series document various events and subsidiary organizations of the Alumni Association. It is the largest series and records from the 1970-1980s comprise the bulk of the material. Two of the major annual events represented in this series are the Alumni Day/Weekend and Homecoming. There are materials documenting Alumni Day/Weekend for the majority of years between 1919 and 1996. The earlier years may only contain a program, while later year may contain correspondence, RSVPs, planning notes and photographs. Other events and symposiums are also included in the series. There are photographs, correspondence, and planning materials of clubs, committees and local branches. Correspondence and day files of Alumni Association staff, awards and scholarships processed by the Alumni Association, student directories and tributes to University Presidents comprise a substantial portion of the series. The Alumni Association offered group travel specials, discounts on insurance and commemorative memorabilia. Please note that some of the photographs are oversized.
  - Association of Graduates Biennial Meeting, 1851-1853 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Dean Anna Pierce, Sunday School Teaching Leaflets, 1882; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Dean Anna Pierce, "Making Friends" Alumni Essay, Correspondence and News Clippings, 1885-1949; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Marilla A. Conklin, Class Notes from Methods in Elocution, 1898 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Mary E. Kennedy, Lesson Plans, Angular Perspectives, Type Forms and Sketches, ca. 1900 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Mary E. Kennedy, Lesson Plans, Drawing, ca. 1900 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Mary E. Kennedy, Lesson Plans, Drawing Notes, ca. 1900 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Mary E. Kennedy, Lesson Plans, La Literature, ca. 1900 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Mary E. Kennedy, Lesson Plans, School Economy, School Government and Child Development, ca. 1900 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Class of 1917 mounted Yearbook Pages (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Ethel M. Houck Correspondence about NYSCT Song Book with John Worley Co., 1917 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - World War I Era Photograph, ca. 1917-1918 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Alumni Day, 1919 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Dean Anna Pierce Correspondence and Clippings, 1919-1921 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Dean Anna Pierce, Dean of Women Annual Report, Correspondence and News Clippings, 1924-1934 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Class of 1922 Mounted Yearbook Pages (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball Team Photograph, 1922 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Alumni Day, 1923 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Harlan H. Homer and Anna Pierce Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Class of 1927 Mounted Yearbook Pages and Photographs (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Class of 1932 Photographs, 1928-1932 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Alumni Day, 1929 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Graduate Council Tenth Birthday Party, 1929 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Women's Horseback Riding Class, 1920s (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Alumni Day, 1930 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Quarter Century Club, Report of Secretary-Treasurer, 1930-1966 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Quarter Century Club, Report of Secretary-Treasurer Inclusions, 1930-1966 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Alumni Day, 1931 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Alumni Day, 1932 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Class of 1932 Mounted Yearbook Pages (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Alumni Day, 1933 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Graduate Council Letters and Minutes, 1933-1954 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Alumni Day, 1934 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Alumni Day, 1935 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Alumni Day, 1936 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - 1944 Alumni Day, 100th Anniversary Material and Preparations, 1936-1944; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Alumni Day, 1937 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Class of 1937 Mounted Yearbook Pages (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Female Varsity Hockey Team Photograph, 1937 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Alumni Day, 1938 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Alumni Day, 1939 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Alumni Day, 1940 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - AEØ Photographs, 1940-1947 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Alumni Day, 1941 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Alumni Day, 1942 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Class of 1942 Mounted Yearbook Pages (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47-48)
  - Alumni Day, 1943 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Alumni Day Suspended due to War, 1945 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Newspaper Clipping, "Veteran Endorsed for Treaty for Troy School Post" (Edward H. Hannan) MA 1932, 1946 September (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Adna W. Risley Memorial Award Committee, [RESTRICTED], 1946-1973 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Alumni Day, 1946 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Alumni Day, 1947 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Class of 1947 Mounted Yearbook Pages (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Photograph Printed Negatives, 1947 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Alumni Day, 1948 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Alumni Day, 1949 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Bibliography of Materials Discussing College and Normal School History, 1949 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Alumni Membership Form, 1940s (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Mounted Yearbook Pages, 1940s (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Numbered Photographs of School, Faculty and Students, ca. 1940s-1960s (Oversized 5)
  - Alumni Day, 1950 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between D. Alvin Eurich and Arvid Burke, 1950 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Membership Form, ca. 1950 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Alumni Day, 1951 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Alumni Day, 1952 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Class of 1952 Mounted Yearbook Pages (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Report on the Memorial Plaque, 1952 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - General Correspondence of Alumni Association Officers, 1952; 1954-1958; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Alumni Day, 1953 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Mounted Yearbook Page, 1953 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Photograph of Medal given to Bertha E. Brimmer, 1954 June 12 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Alumni Day, 1954 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Alumni Day, 1955 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Alumni Day, 1956 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Alumni Day, 1957 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Mounted Yearbook Pages and Photograph, 1957 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Alumni Day, 1958 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Photograph of Students and Alumni, 1958 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Alumni Day, 1959 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Photograph of Homecoming Committee, ca. 1950s (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)